const quizData = [
  {
    question: "Which AWS service provides scalable cloud computing capacity in the cloud?",
    options: ["Amazon EC2", "Amazon S3", "Amazon RDS", "Amazon Redshift"],
    answer: "Amazon EC2"
  },
  {
    question: "What does 'S3' stand for in Amazon S3?",
    options: ["Simple Storage Service", "Scalable Server Storage", "Secure Storage Solution", "Systematic Storage Service"],
    answer: "Simple Storage Service"
  },
  {
    question: "Which AWS service is a fully managed NoSQL database service?",
    options: ["Amazon RDS", "Amazon DynamoDB", "Amazon Redshift", "Amazon Aurora"],
    answer: "Amazon DynamoDB"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of AWS's content delivery network (CDN) service?",
    options: ["Amazon Glacier", "Amazon S3", "Amazon CloudFront", "Amazon EBS"],
    answer: "Amazon CloudFront"
  },
  {
    question: "Which AWS service allows users to send, receive, and store email?",
    options: ["Amazon SES", "Amazon SNS", "Amazon SQS", "Amazon EC2"],
    answer: "Amazon SES"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of AWS's service for building and managing virtualized environments?",
    options: ["Amazon VPC", "Amazon ECS", "Amazon EMR", "Amazon EKS"],
    answer: "Amazon VPC"
  },
  {
    question: "Which AWS service enables you to set up a private, dedicated connection between your data center and AWS?",
    options: ["Amazon Direct Connect", "Amazon VPN", "Amazon Route 53", "Amazon WorkSpaces"],
    answer: "Amazon Direct Connect"
  },
  {
    question: "What does 'IAM' stand for in AWS IAM?",
    options: ["Internet Access Management", "Identity and Access Management", "Integrated Account Management", "Internal Authorization Model"],
    answer: "Identity and Access Management"
  },
  {
    question: "Which AWS service provides scalable database storage in the cloud?",
    options: ["Amazon Aurora", "Amazon DynamoDB", "Amazon RDS", "Amazon Redshift"],
    answer: "Amazon RDS"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of AWS's service for building serverless applications?",
    options: ["Amazon Lambda", "Amazon API Gateway", "Amazon ECS", "Amazon EKS"],
    answer: "Amazon Lambda"
  },
  {
    question: "Which AWS service allows users to process large datasets?",
    options: ["Amazon Redshift", "Amazon DynamoDB", "Amazon S3", "Amazon Glacier"],
    answer: "Amazon Redshift"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of AWS's service for automated security assessment?",
    options: ["Amazon Inspector", "Amazon GuardDuty", "AWS Config", "Amazon Macie"],
    answer: "Amazon Inspector"
  },
  {
    question: "Which AWS service provides a fully managed file system?",
    options: ["Amazon EFS", "Amazon S3", "Amazon Glacier", "Amazon EBS"],
    answer: "Amazon EFS"
  }
];

export default quizData;
